servcorp.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy and Data Security | Servcorp

## Privacy

When you visit the Servcorp website ([http://www.servcorp.com](http://www.servcorp.com/)) we make every effort to help you maintain control over your personal information on the Internet. Listed below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site.   

Servcorp supports the mission of the Online Privacy Alliance (OPA). The OPA promotes trust and confidence on the Internet by advocating ethical online business practices. Further information about this program is available at http://www.privacyalliance.com. Servcorp is also subject to the National Privacy Principles (NPPs) as outlined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).  

This statement discloses the privacy guidelines for the entire Servcorp website. For more information about our privacy or information usage guidelines, contact us at [offices@servcorp.com](mailto:offices@servcorp.com) and put the word Privacy in the subject line.   

  1. Who does this Privacy Policy apply to?

Servcorp collects personal information from a variety of sources. Servcorp does not collect sensitive information. This Privacy Policy applies to any personal information collected by Servcorp about:  

    prospective employees

    individuals who are customers of Servcorp USA clients

    clients

    business partners

    suppliers

    contracts

    shareholders

    other people who may come into contact with Servcorp USA through its network of executive suites   

Servcorp is not bound by the NPPs in relation to its treatment of employee records if the treatment is directly related to a current or former employment relationship between Servcorp and an employee.   

  1. Requests for Personal Information

In any area of our website where Servcorp asks you to provide personal information that will enable us to enhance your site visit or to follow up with you after your visit, it is completely optional for you to participate.

For example, we request information from you when you:   

    Request information about a product or service

    Sign up for a virtual office

    Provide feedback in an online form   

In each of the instances above, Servcorp may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address and type of business, as well as other similar information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.   

  1. Use of Personal Information

The personal information you provide will be kept confidential, unless otherwise stated, and used to support your customer relationship with Servcorp. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on this site and alert you to product upgrades, new documentation, updated web information and other new products and services from Servcorp.

Agents or contractors of Servcorp who have access to your information are required to keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Servcorp. Servcorp may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.   

  1. Disclosure of Information

Servcorp does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site. This includes any licensing forms or e-mail lists.   

  1. Updating Personal Information

You can request the individual information that Servcorp has collected about you via the Internet or have factual inaccuracies in this information corrected by contacting [offices@servcorp.com](mailto:offices@servcorp.com).   

  1. Security of Personal Information

Servcorp will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorized access, modification and disclosure. Servcorp uses industry standard safeguards to ensure the security of personal information through physical, electronic and managerial procedures. Servcorp will not sell, rent, loan, trade, lease or license any personal information collected at any of our offices.

When Servcorp no longer requires personal information, it will safely destroy the information and delete it from its systems.   

  1. Customized Experience

The Servcorp website does not use cookies.   

  1. What Else Should I Know About My Privacy?

Third party Internet sites and services accessible through this site have separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Servcorp has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Be aware that if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.   

  1. Access to Personal Information

You or a third party nominated by you in writing may request access to any of the personal information that Servcorp holds about you. Upon your written request, Servcorp will provide access to the personal information that it holds about you, unless there is an exemption which applies under the Privacy Act.   

Your request for access will be dealt with in a reasonable time. Servcorp may charge you a fee to cover the reasonable cost of retrieval and the supply of the information to you. If Servcorp refuses your request for access, it will provide you with reasons for the refusal.

Servcorp may provide access to personal information without your consent only in certain prescribed circumstances, including but not limited to:   

    emergency situations

    specified Federal and State agencies and to comply with legislative requirements

    law enforcement

    lessening or preventing a serious and imminent threat to an individual's life, health or safety or a serious threat to public health or public safety   

  1. How to Contact Us

If you wish to gain access to or correct your personal information or make a complaint about a breach of your privacy, you should contact: Telephone: +1 (404) 736-9200

Mail: Terminus 200, 3333 Piedmont Road, Suite 2050, ﻿﻿Atlanta, GA 30305 USA

Email: [offices@servcorp.com](mailto:offices@servcorp.com)  

Website: [http://www.servcorp.com](http://www.servcorp.com/)  

Servcorp will respond to your query or complaint as soon as possible. Servcorp reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.

**Servcorp has an average rating of  4.9 out of 5 stars.  The rating is based on 476 reviews on trustpilot.com**
